Deploy your project to Netlify

USAGE
  $ netlify deploy [options]

OPTIONS
  --alias <name>Specifies the alias for deployment, the string at the beginning
       of the deploy subdomain. Useful for creating predictable deployment
       URLs. Avoid setting an alias string to the same value as a deployed
       branch. `alias` doesn?셳 create a branch deploy and can?셳 be used in
       conjunction with the branch subdomain feature. Maximum 37 characters.
  --context <context>Specify a deploy context for environment variables read
       during the build ("production", "deploy-preview", "branch-deploy",
       "dev") or `branch:your-branch` where `your-branch` is the name of a
       branch (default: dev)
  --create-site [name]Create a new site and deploy to it. Optionally specify a
       name, otherwise a random name will be generated. Requires --team flag if
       you have multiple teams.
  -d, --dir <path>Specify a folder to deploy
  --filter <app>For monorepos, specify the name of the application to run the
       command in
  -f, --functions <folder>Specify a functions folder to deploy
  -h, --helpdisplay help for command
  --jsonOutput deployment data as JSON
  -m, --message <message>A short message to include in the deploy log
  --no-buildDo not run build command before deploying. Only use this if you
       have no need for a build or your project has already been built.
  -O, --openOpen project after deploy (default: false)
  --prod-if-unlockedDeploy to production if unlocked, create a draft otherwise
       (default: false)
  --debugPrint debugging information
  --auth <token>Netlify auth token - can be used to run this command without
       logging in
  -p, --prodDeploy to production (default: false)
  -s, --site <name-or-id>A project name or ID to deploy to
  --skip-functions-cacheIgnore any functions created as part of a previous
       `build` or `deploy` commands, forcing them to be bundled again as part
       of the deployment (default: false)
  --team <slug>Specify team slug when creating a site. Only works with
       --create-site flag.
  --timeout <number>Timeout to wait for deployment to finish
  --triggerTrigger a new build of your project on Netlify without uploading
       local files

DESCRIPTION
  
  Builds and deploys your project to Netlify. Creates a draft deploy by default.
  Use --prod to deploy directly to your live site.
  
  The deploy command will:
  - Build your project (unless --no-build is specified)
  - Upload static files, functions, and edge functions
  - Process redirects and headers from netlify.toml or _redirects/_headers files
  - Provide deploy and function logs URLs
  
  For detailed configuration options, see the Netlify documentation.

EXAMPLES
  $ netlify deploy
  $ netlify deploy --site my-first-project
  $ netlify deploy --no-build # Deploy without running a build first
  $ netlify deploy --prod
  $ netlify deploy --prod --open
  $ netlify deploy --prod-if-unlocked
  $ netlify deploy --message "A message with an $ENV_VAR"
  $ netlify deploy --auth $NETLIFY_AUTH_TOKEN
  $ netlify deploy --trigger
  $ netlify deploy --context deploy-preview
  $ netlify deploy --create-site my-new-site --team my-team # Create site and deploy


For more information about Netlify deploys, see https://docs.netlify.com/site-deploys/overview/

